icreatived.com 2019-01-01

# PRIVACY POLICY - iCreatived

**Privacy Policy**

Icreatived maintains the practice of protecting your privacy and keeps the information safe that you may provide us through our Website.  
Our Privacy Policy applies solely upon the information collected on Icreatived, its usage and circumstances in case of need to disclose the information to third parties.

**Collecting Information And Its Usage**

Usually, Icreatived collects the following two types of information about our users:  
Information Provided To Us That Personally Identifies You  
Icreatived is the sole owner of the personally identifiable information that you provide us. We only have access to information that our users voluntarily send us, for instance, name, e-mail address, or other direct communication information. The choice of providing this information entirely depends upon you.  
This information provided by you is used to respond to the reasons for contacting us, such as participation in a particular activity, the benefits we may offer, or access to certain contents on our website, and improve our services for your benefit.  
Information Collected Automatically That Does Not Identify You Personally  
When you visit our website and browse through it, read pages, or download information, we collect and store certain information about your visit, automatically, such as the Internet domain (for example, website.com, if you use a private Internet access account), your IP address (IP address is a set of numbers that is automatically generated to your computer while surfing the website), pages visited, date and time of access, type of browser and operating system used to access the site, and the address of the website you linked to our site from.  
Though this information does not mention about your personal identification, but regarding the usage of your data. This information is gathered and used to count the number and type of visitors to the different pages on our website. This helps us make our site more useful to the visitors like you.

**Security Of Your Information**

We take preventive measures to protect your information submitted by you via the website. It is kept protective against the loss, misuse and alteration under our control. We store data on the computers/servers that are kept in a secure environment.  
While we strive to protect your personal information and privacy, however, it is advised that we cannot guarantee or warranty the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online. We are also not responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information.  
We Keep Updating  
We make modifications to our Privacy Policy from time to time as per the new technologies, for protecting the information, and when found applicable, we upgrade our information security systems.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data that lets you to store your information on the hard drive and allows the website to retrieve it when you visit the site.  
Icreatived places a little text file called “Cookie” on your hard drive to save your comment’s information, thereby saving time every time you visit our website. Other websites cannot use or view the cookies set by us.  
With the help of cookies, we track and target the interests of the site visitors to be able to enhance the experience on the website and store their email and other contact information in order to save time by not having to re-type it when making comments.  
We monitor our users’ activity which helps us in improving our website and the services provided to you. In order to disable the use of cookies, you can change your Internet browser settings, so that your browser does not accept them.

**Links**

Icreatived contains links to other sites. It is to be noted that we are not responsible for the content or privacy policy when you link to other sites, because you become subject to the privacy policy of the new website. Therefore, we request our users to read and understand the privacy statements of another site when they leave our site.

**Liability Restriction**

Icreatived does not claim promises, or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of our website contents. We specifically disclaim liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this website.

**Privacy Police Changes**

We may change the Privacy Policy statements as and when required, and notify about it at this URL. The changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective from the time it is posted.  
Continuing with the usage of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall be taken as your acceptance thereof.
